[MUSIC]
>> Hey, look at that.
Let's go.
What do you think it is?
>> It looks like a giant space dumpster.
>> Let's open it up.
[MUSIC]
>> Okay, let's get out of here.
[LAUGH]
>> All right, we're at home.
>> Here we go, we go, we're free.
[MUSIC]
>> Uh-oh, morning friends, let me get out of here.
>> Oh, it's good to be free after 10,000 years.
>> Here you evil, let me help you.
>> Walk with me, talk with me.
>> You may be stepping upon all your networks.
Get out of my way, muggy face.
[MUSIC]
>> [LAUGH]
>> Don't leave, you'll miss my coming out party.
That's when I destroy the nearest planet.
>> [LAUGH]
[MUSIC]
>> It's a tremendous Saturday in Angel Grove
as a big yellow boost after earning as a kid of the Angel Grove
youth center, Jim and Juice Bar.
Keep those fruit shakes, flow and earn it.
[MUSIC]
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Nice recovery, Zach.
>> Thanks for teaching me Jason.
>> No problem.
[MUSIC]
>> That was awesome, Kimberly.
>> Thanks, Jenny.
[MUSIC]
>> Hey, Bella.
>> Yo, Billy, what's up?
>> Well, I think I'm mentally and physically prepared for
my first karate class.
[MUSIC]
>> No, look who's here.
Ball and snow.
>> Hi, girls.
How about that double date we talked about?
>> Yeah.
[LAUGH]
>> What about?
>> Sorry, guys.
[MUSIC]
>> What's the matter?
We're not good enough for you.
>> Leave us a loan book.
>> Yeah, make me.
[MUSIC]
>> Hey, thank you.
>> Hey, you heard what you said.
>> What do you know?
The dancer wants to be a fighter.
>> It's okay, Zach.
We can handle these two.
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
Let's show them some karate moves, go.
[MUSIC]
>> You guys should definitely join Jason's karate class.
>> Yeah, I like it.
>> Good.
>> Woo, they start making karate controllers.
>> Yes, Mike, we.
>> I'll lead them down and make the earth yours and press.
>> [SOUND]
>> And one.
>> Two.
>> Like three.
>> Punch four.
>> And continue.
>> Yeah.
[MUSIC]
>> Paroa.
>> Have a try this.
[MUSIC]
>> I'm just not good at this.
>> Billy, don't worry.
I mean, even I was a beginner ones.
>> Jim B.
>> All right, class, what is it?
The martial arts helps us to develop.
>> Billy?
>> Courage, kindness, integrity, fitness, loyalty, and discipline.
>> That's good.
I remember I said very quickly.
>> Hey.
[MUSIC]
>> Teach us how to beat people up.
>> Yeah.
[MUSIC]
>> The martial arts was not developed to hurt others.
>> We did not sign up for a geeky karate class.
>> Okay, walk.
Maybe you're ready for some more advanced training techniques.
>> No.
>> Okay.
>> Try this.
[MUSIC]
>> Side pick.
>> Anything you can do, I can do better, baby.
[MUSIC]
>> Tornado kick.
>> [APPLAUSE]
[MUSIC]
>> Billy, I'm telling you, for your first lesson, you did really well.
>> I did?
>> Yeah, we were watching.
>> I don't know if I've got what it takes.
>> It's all a state of mind, Billy.
You don't need to be strong for martial arts.
>> Yeah, man, I saw up here.
>> Hey, guys.
>> Hey, honey.
>> Who ordered the spinach juice?
[MUSIC]
>> Hey, me.
>> It's earthquake.
Everybody stay calm.
[MUSIC]
>> I'm sorry, boy.
>> Something tells me this is no earthquake.
>> Danger, danger.
It's the big one.
I know it will all be destroyed.
>> Calm down, Nova.
It's Rita.
She's escaped and she's attacking the planet.
>> Yeah, yeah, what do we do?
What brought to us five overbearing and over emotional human?
>> No, not that, not teenagers.
>> That's correct, don't, huh?
>> I was afraid of that.
[MUSIC]
>> Oh, my gosh, we're coming at it.
It's too weird.
Hold on.
[MUSIC]
>> Isn't exactly the mall, is it?
>> This place is magnificent.
>> I don't get it.
I'll wind up here.
>> I just want to know where here it is.
>> Well, maybe the answer's in these controls.
>> No, no, no, don't touch that one.
>> Whoa.
[MUSIC]
>> A fully sentient multifunctional automaton.
Never seen anything like it.
[MUSIC]
>> Welcome, humans.
>> Uh-uh.
>> So, who are you?
>> Like, what are you?
>> I am Zordon, an interdimensional being caught in a time war.
>> And my name is Alpha Phi.
>> Excuse me, but like somebody come back to Earth and pick me up because I am totally confused.
>> It's quite simple, my dear.
This planet is under attack, and I have brought you here to save it.
>> Oh, yeah, right.
>> Ah, a non-believer.
Look behind you at the viewing globe.
Your doubts will be answered in the images you see.
[MUSIC]
>> This is Rita Rapulsa, an intergalactic sorceress who has bent on controlling the universe.
With her henchmen and puddy controllers, she plans to conquer her.
>> [LAUGH]
>> What does all of this have to do with that?
>> You've been chosen to form an elite team to battle Rita.
Each of you will be given access to extraordinary powers drawn from the ancient creatures you call dinosaur.
>> Dinosaurs.
[MUSIC]
>> Behold, the keys to your power.
>> Whoa, what are these?
>> Those are your power orphans.
When in danger, raise them to the sky, calling the name of your dinosaur.
And you will morph into a formidable fighting force known to want it all as the power ranges.
>> Morph?
>> Metamorphosis.
>> That means to change.
>> As power ranges, you will have access to a universe of power and
will command a fleet of fighting machines called swords.
>> I don't get it.
>> Jason, hold and powerful.
You shall command the Tyrannosaurus dinosaurs.
Zachary, you are clever and brave.
You shall command the mastodon dinosaurs.
>> [NOISE]
>> Kimberly, graceful and smart.
The tarot-actyl dinosaurs shall be yours.
Billy, patient and wives.
You shall command the powerful triceratops dinosaur.
>> Streamy, fearless and agile, the saber-tooth tiger dinosaur will be only your command.
>> Observe the viewing glow.
Just as the final you work together, soak your swords.
When you need help, you need only to turn to the power of the dinosaurs,
which will come together to form the mighty Megasaur.
[MUSIC]
>> Power movers?
Megasaur?
>> I'm up.
This is just too weird for me.
I tell you what, it's been real, but I gotta go.
>> Yeah, see ya.
[MUSIC]
>> Y'all coming?
>> Jason.
>> What?
>> Let's go, man.
>> Yeah.
>> Very well then.
Let the power protect you.
>> Well, now that didn't go very well, did it.
I, I, I, I.
[MUSIC]
>> Great.
You could have sent us back into town.
[MUSIC]
>> Swordon, I'm surprised, teenagers.
So you think you can stop me, do you?
Fitstar, hurry up with us, buddy, betrotors.
>> Yes, you'll evil backness.
I'm molding the last ones now.
>> Those parties will make space to start with those kids.
>> And the beauty is, if they don't, we can always make more.
Out into the months, the matter they go, 10 seconds should do it.
[MUSIC]
>> Now, my buddies prepare to get those teenagers.
[LAUGH]
>> Guys, we shouldn't have left.
I mean, he chose us to save the world.
I say we do it.
>> Do you really think we can?
>> Guys, I mean, you don't even know what you're talking about.
We're talking to a giant floating head.
>> Those stupid teenagers don't know who they're messing with.
[MUSIC]
Get the buddies, it's time.
>> All right, take that.
[MUSIC]
>> Where'd it go?
>> Where was that?
[MUSIC]
>> Look out.
>> Jack, right.
He's too alive.
[MUSIC]
>> Hey.
>> Wait.
[MUSIC]
>> The state is too weird.
>> What did we do now?
>> Sort of understood these power morphers.
Give us power.
Let's do it.
[MUSIC]
>> Masked it on.
>> Triceratops.
>> Save a two-ziker.
[MUSIC]
>> All right.
>> Do it on.
They need to better morphuses.
>> Hello.
>> Hello, welcome to Angel Bro City.
Please don't just send down Gold Hawk.
>> Right away, he's going on.
>> We're teleporting again.
>> Where are we going?
>> We're gonna save the world.
>> Go, go, go, go, go.
>> All right, let's do it.
>> Go, go, go, go.
>> Yeah.
>> You're welcome.
>> Thank you.
>> What?
>> Yeah.
[MUSIC]
>> That star zone stupid puddies are getting beat.
>> My a bunch of people may stick with, never say that.
>> How about we can go to our beat with your wand?
>> I always have to do everything myself.
>> Yes.
>> I'll tell you later.
>> Oh.
>> Yeah.
>> Magic wand.
Make my gold arms roll.
[MUSIC]
>> Look at him, that dude's shoes.
>> Yeah.
>> Back up, bring face.
The good guys are here.
Get off our planet.
>> Good for the pillow reaper.
>> And we're not backing down.
>> Yeah.
>> Good and sore pose.
[MUSIC]
>> Let's do it.
>> It's not going up.
>> It's not here.
>> This is kicking.
>> This is Billy.
All systems go.
>> Reading here, ready to rock.
>> Hey, nice stereo.
[MUSIC]
>> Big is going cold.
>> This is amazing.
It's going to have a drive to stay.
>> All right.
>> Fighting too.
It's almost like second nature too.
[MUSIC]
>> All right guys, let's go get him.
>> Right.
[MUSIC]
>> You and your weapons are no match for me.
>> All right guys, let's see what this baby can do.
[MUSIC]
>> All right.
>> All right guys, power it up.
>> Everybody make us work better.
[MUSIC]
>> Thank you Lord, see what kind of thing he is.
>> Thanks again.
[MUSIC]
>> Jason, that blow didn't even phase him.
>> Yeah.
>> He's coming at us.
[MUSIC]
>> Let's go.
>> I'll be back.
[MUSIC]
>> I can't believe I beat him back.
>> You don't, you're both what you should have held.
>> Go Lord, you failed.
>> It won't happen again, you're fresh.
>> Shut up, I gotta hate it.
>> It was amazing.
>> Congratulations on a job well done.
Now that you have become power Rangers, you must follow three basic rules.
Or lose the protection of the power.
First, never use your power for personal gain.
Second, never escalate a battle unless reader forces you.
And finally, keep your identity secret.
No one may know you are a power ranger.
>> Wait a second.
>> Yes, Zachary, what is it?
>> I'm not sure we're all up to this.
>> I mean, we were pretty lucky this time.
>> Luck had nothing to do with it.
The five of you have come together to form as fine a group of superheroes as there has ever been.
>> No way.
>> You've been throwing extraordinary experience together.
You need each other now.
And the world needs you.
>> Yeah, all right, I'm in.
Me too.
>> You can count on me.
Affirmative.
>> I don't know you guys.
I mean, the outfits are cool and everything.
But my hair gets all tangled up inside the helmet.
I don't think I can do it.
>> Oh, no.
>> See, I'm not literally knowing.
>> No!
>> Not!
[MUSIC]
>> Humor, what a concept.
[LAUGH]
>> Let's do it.
[MUSIC]
>> Power Rangers!